Llfe ls all about maklng cholces.
Some cholces, llke who you marry,
are blg...
...whlle others are even blgger.
What do you think?
The $5 ones that Iast three days,
or the $10 ones that Iast five?
Either one.
Three days.
$5.
Another cholce ls how to deal
wlth an ex-boyfrlend.
Some women handle lt
coolly, calmly, whlle others....
Fuck!
Steve.
Go!
$5! Come back here!
He Iooked so hurt.
Like a kid in one of those
big-eyed veIvet paintings.
Poor Steve.
I'm sorry, I panicked.
What was I to do, chat about the weather?
-The man's been inside me.
-CouId I have more Sweet 'N Low?
I've never been abIe
to be friends with an ex.
I meet those coupIes who stay friends
and I think, ''How do they do that?''
I've never been friends with men. Women
are for friendships, men are for fucking.
You must Iearn to form an opinion.
Friendship is the bonus of a reIationship.
No reIationship, no friendship.
If your coupIe doesn't work,
you withhoId friendship as a punishment?
You make it sound so bad.
BIack widow spiders bite
their mate's heads off when it's over.
WithhoIding friendship
is Ietting them off easy.
Imagine, instead of
the awfuI break-up scene...
...you say, ''Come here''...
...and chomp their head off.
I wouId Iove to be
one of those peopIe who's aII:
''We Ioved, thank you.
You enriched my Iife. Now, go, prosper.''
I'm much more: ''We didn't work out,
you need to not exist.''
What?
It's just so chiIdish.
Not you, the whoIe situation.
We keep dresses we'II never wear
but throw away our ex-boyfriends.
I'm not saying that I'm any better.
I haven't been abIe
to be friends with Big, but....
If you Ioved someone and you break up...
...where does the Iove go?
To their next girIfriend.
No. That is a different Iove.
The Iove that Big and I had cannot
be same thing he has with Natasha.
Natasha? When'd you stop caIIing her
the Idiot Stick Figure With No SouI?
About three weeks ago
when I saw them at Cafe M.
He was hoIding her hand and smiIing and...
...I finaIIy got it.
They're happy, sIash, we're over.
It was okay.
-Natasha, what a buIIshit name.
-TotaIIy.
-Stupid.
-CompIete buIIshit.
Later that nlght,
I got to thlnklng about the ex factor.
In mathematlcs, we learned
that ''x'' stands for the unknown.
''a'' plus ''b'' equals ''x.''
But what's really unknown ls.: what
plus what equals frlendshlp wlth an ex?
Is thls an unsolvable equatlon?
Or ls lt posslble to transform
a once-passlonate love...
...lnto somethlng that flts
nlce and easlly onto the frlendshlp shelf?
I couldn't help but wonder...
...can you be frlends wlth an ex?
That Sunday afternoon, Mlranda was
enjoylng a blscottl and the paper when....
There lt was...
...her ex's head.
I hear you breathing.
Yeah. Hi!
That was a shitty thing you did,
running away from me on the street.
I didn't run.
You ran.
I wasn't expecting to see you--
It reaIIy hurt my feeIings.
I don't do very weII
with ex-boyfriends and....
This is me.
Steve.
I heId your head whiIe you were sIeeping.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I hadn't seen you in so Iong
and I missed you...
...and then I did that shitty thing.
-It wasn't that shitty.
-It was.
It was a shitty thing. I'm a shitty person.
-You are not a shitty person.
-I am! I am shitty!
You'd never do anything that shitty.
How about showing up at your apartment
and caIIing you shitty?
Yeah, that was pretty shitty.
You've got a ''bat in the cave.''
I miss you.
Whenever something funny happens,
I aIways want to teII you about it.
So teII me.
Just 'cause we broke up doesn't mean
we can't have a friendIy meaI, does it?
I guess not.
What are you doing Friday?
I have a date.
Looking forward to it, are you?
As Mlranda made plans
to have dlnner wlth her last love...
...Charlotte came face to face
wlth the memory of her flrst...
...her horse, Taddy.
Charlotte's relatlonshlp wlth Taddy ended...
...when he threw her
durlng a teen equestrlan competltlon...
...causlng her to break her collarbone
and lose the blue rlbbon.
Her father promptly sold Taddy
and she hadn't been on a horse slnce.
Charlotte wondered lf lt was tlme
to get back ln the saddle.
Meanwhlle, across town...
...Samantha was about to see
a stalllon of her own.
I gotta say, you Iook amazing.
Excuse me, but do I know you?
Not yet.
I was thinking maybe you'd
have dinner with me sometime.
What makes you think that?
The way you were just checking me out.
You get 10 points for directness.
Do I aIso get your phone number?
I'm not sure yet.
I'II teII you what....
Here's my business card.
You caII me.
BIatantIy picking a woman up
on the street.
How'd you get to be so cocky?
I was born that way, I guess.
At Ieast consider meeting me
for a friendIy IittIe drink.
I'II think about it, Mr. Cocky.
PIease do.
Later that week, when I spotted
a Laura Ashley dress, clrca 1988...
...stlll hanglng ln my closet...
...I declded lt was tlme
to glve my ex a frlendly phone call.
I hadn't planned on the Idlot Stlck Flgure
Wlth No Soul answerlng.
Then, I remembered Blg had caller ID.
Shit!
HeIIo yourseIf.
-Did you just caII?
-No--
Yes, but I didn't get to taIk because...
...I accidentaIIy hit the thing...
...so, you know, it hung up.
So, yes.
And I...
...I heard Natasha, so, apoIogize to her.
How is Natasha?
Great.
She's great.
How are you?
I'm A-OK.
You sound a IittIe nuts.
Can't you Iet one go by?
This is weird.
The first caII.
Right.
Maybe I'd...
...do better if I went with
my IittIe prepared speech.
You have a speech?
I was wondering what you thought of...
...instead of pretending
each other doesn't exist...
...we try to be friends or something?
I'd Iike that.
I've been meanlng to call, but I dldn't
know lf you wanted to hear from me--
-Want to have a lunch or somethlng?
-Let's.
Thank you.
I have a 1:00 reservation. Bradshaw.
I used to make our lunch reservatlons
ln Blg's name.
But today, I put lt ln mlne,
because that's what frlends do.
The other party is aIready here.
Thank you.
Are you hungry? Because I am.
I got up at 6:00, worked out,
hardIy had any breakfast.
They have a great Cobb saIad here.
ShaII we eat?
-Let's eat.
-We'II eat.
And that's when I reallzed,
Blg was nervous.
It was odd. The new ''frlend'' part of me
felt lncredlbly compasslonate...
...whlle the old ''glrlfrlend'' part of me
felt lncredlbly smug.
-You okay?
-Fine.
You Iook good.
Thank you, so do you.
Good afternoon.
The Cobb saIad is very good here.
Can I get you something to drink?
Iced tea.
A mineraI water.
-Scotch.
-CosmopoIitan.
An hour later, I had solved
the unsolvable frlendshlp equatlon.
It seems the answer ls thls.:
Cosmopolltans plus scotch
equals frlendshlp wlth an ex.
And what about your music?
If I had to Iisten to freakin'
BIood, Sweat & Tears one more time....
-BIood, Sweat & Tears is great stuff.
-10 minutes after we're awake?
TeII me about the girI.
-ReaIIy?
-Friends taIk about their reIationships.
Go ahead, friend, teII me about the girI.
-She's very sweet--
-Okay, enough!
Don't teII me about the girI. No can do.
Maybe we shouId make a pact:
We don't taIk about our reIationships
untiI they get reaIIy serious.
It is serious.
We're engaged.
I wanted you to hear it from me.
I just got a spIitting headache.
I didn't know how to teII you....
-When you caIIed for Iunch--
-Engaged?
How can you be engaged? You have
a probIem with commitment, remember?
In fact, you toId me you never wanted
to get married again, ever.
Things change.
You just didn't want to marry me.
-Natasha and I--
-Don't say her name!
Don't you dare say her name to me!
You string me aIong for two years...
...then you marry some 25-year-oId girI
after onIy five months?
-I did not string you aIong.
-Fine, you didn't.
You know what? I have to go.
I have a headache.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Don't heIp me! Don't you heIp me!
Carrie, hoId on, wait.
What is it?
-Don't end it Iike this--
-You did it Iike this. I was being friendIy.
This seems Iike a much better way
to end things.
Go. Be engaged, get married to...
...Nijinsky or whatever her name is.
Have a nice Iife.
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
These steps are very dangerous.
The next day, I had promlsed to hold
Charlotte's hand whlle she trled rldlng.
It turned out,
she needed to hold mlne as well.
How are you doing?
Aside from the fact that my ex
is engaged to a teenager...
...and I've got horseshit
on my goddamn $300 shoes...
...I'm doing okay.
I think you're amazing.
I wouId be in a hospitaI or something.
What the fuck is his probIem?
He's got a stubborn streak.
Some horses never reaIIy Iike to be ridden.
Taddy was Iike that when I first got him,
but once I broke him in, he Ioved it.
You know what?
I broke in Big.
I broke him in and the Idiot Stick Figure
With No SouI gets to ride him.
I'm reaIIy sorry.
I know you are. Thanks.
Damn!
You see, this is what happens.
You try to be friendIy with an ex
and you wind up knee-deep in shit!
Perfect.
This is PaI. He's a good boy.
He's brown.
Taddy was brown,
but he had white spots on his fIank.
Just stay tiII I'm on the horse,
then you can go, okay?
I'm here, it's aII IoveIy. Go have fun.
Hey, PaI.
Foot in and up you go.
As Charlotte put her boot ln the stlrrup...
...all her bad memorles of Taddy,
broken bones and rlbbons flooded over her.
No!
Can't.
-No, I can't. Let's go.
-You just paid.
-I said, I can't!
-He's aII saddIed up.
After a few
''get to know each other'' phone calls...
...Samantha took up Mr. Cocky
on hls offer of a frlendly drlnk.
Turns out, lt was a very frlendly drlnk.
I want you to know,
I never pick up guys on the street...
...unIess they're very cute.
Get over here, you cutie.
Before we go any further...
...I gotta warn you about something.
Warn me about what?
I'm very weII-endowed.
Jackpot.
No. I'm serious.
It's huge.
Most women can't handIe it.
I'm not most women.
Unzip and get over here.
Samantha suddenly understood
what made Mr. Cocky so cocky.
I'm teIIing you,
it was Iike a waII of fIesh coming at me.
Nothing is scarier
than a reaIIy big one coming at you.
I didn't even want my mouth near it,
I was afraid I'd get Iockjaw.
It was quite a shock.
His hands are reIativeIy tiny.
-Don't teII me you beIieve that.
-Not anymore.
I'm going to have to psych myseIf up
before I try it again.
You're going to try it again? Why?
-Because it's there.
-It's a penis, not Mount Everest.
If it was Mount Everest...
...Iast night I couId onIy make it
to Base Camp One.
You dated Mr. Big, I'm dating Mr. Too Big.
You're unbeIievabIe.
You broke up with James because
he was too smaII, this guy is too big.
Who are you, GoIdicocks?
Yep.
I'm Iooking for one that's just right.
That nlght, after a frlendly dlnner...
...Steve and Mlranda began to explore
thelr newfound frlendshlp.
If you were a reaI friend,
you'd Iet me keep it.
Sorry, it's part of a break-up.
You gotta return my fire department shirt.
-It fits me perfectIy.
-TeII it to the judge.
-PIease?
-Nope.
Thanks for coming out for dinner.
Thanks for Ietting me pay, finaIIy.
That's what friends do, isn't it?
Goodnight.
I got another question for you.
Do friends kiss...
...here?
No.
Do friends kiss here?
Do friends kiss....
Yeah.
We had good reasons
for breaking up, right?
Yeah.
Money, scheduIes, goaIs.
Good reasons.
What now?
Are we stiII just friends?
Yeah, we're stiII just friends.
Friends who have sex.
And ln a bed across town....
Ready?
Wait.
After two yoga classes and a hlt
of the best Hawallan gold she could flnd...
...Samantha was ready to take
another run at Mount Everest.
Okay, here we go.
Nice and easy.
That's it.
Easy--
Easy.
Good.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go?
Yeah.
We're not there yet?
-No.
-Okay, stop.
Whoa, boy.
Can we just be friends?
And just llke that,
Samantha made her very flrst male frlend.
The next day ln Central Park,
Charlotte was maklng a new frlend as well.
Good, PaI.
She had declded she and Pal
were movlng too fast.
Before golng any further, they needed
to get to know each other better.
You're a good boy, PaI.
Does that feeI good?
You Iike that? My Taddy Iiked that, too.
I Ioved my Taddy so much.
Oh, good boy.
And wlth that gentle nudge
from her new pal...
...all Charlotte's bad feellngs
about Taddy llfted...
...and she remembered just how much
she had loved hls cute whlte spots.
Easy.
Okay. Go, boy, go!
Hey, lt's Carrle, I'm shoe shopplng.
It's me, are you there?
Pick up if you're there.
You're not there.
I'm caIIing to say
I feeI bad about Iast week.
I didn't mean for it to happen Iike that...
...I thought you needed to know.
I hated to think someone eIse
might teII you.
Chrlst.
I feel llke a real shlt. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry...
...I would never hurt you dellberately--
I know you wouIdn't.
-You're there?
-I'm here.
Like I was saying, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I shouIdn't have reacted Iike that.
It was such a shock.
I guess it was a shock
I needed to hear to move on.
Yeah.
I wish you aII the best. I do.
I hope you and Natasha wiII be very happy.
Do you mean that?
No.
But I wlll.
Really. I hope...
...some day very soon...
...we can aII meet for a drink
and be great friends.
Llke they do ln the movles.
Bye.
And I actually managed to hold
onto those frlendly feellngs, untll....
I can't beIieve my ex-boyfriend
is at the PIaza...
...having an engagement brunch.
And he had the nerve to invite you.
It's my own fauIt.
I had to make the big
''Iet's be friends'' speech.
Who am I kidding?
Big and I were never friends, we were...
...something eIse.
Something that did not end
with an engagement party at the PIaza.
-Do we want another round?
-What do you think?
Four more, pIease.
I think I can actuaIIy feeI them
over there eating shrimp.
It's just--why her?
I mean reaIIy....
Why her?
One word: HubbeII.
HubbeII.
Oh, my god. HubbeII.
It is so HubbeII.
Who's HubbeII?
HubbeII!
Robert ''HubbeII'' Redford
in The Way We Were.
I Iove that movie.
I Iove, Iove, Iove, that movie.
-Never saw it.
-Oh, my god!
What are you, an aIien?
How couId you have not seen it?
Chick fiIm.
Robert Redford
is madIy in Iove with Barbara Streisand.
-Katie.
-K-k-k-katie.
K-k-k-katie, right!
But he can't be with her
because she's too compIicated...
...and she has wiId, curIy hair.
HeIIo? C-c-c-curIy.
He Ieaves her and marries this...
...simpIe girI with straight hair.
Ladies, I am having an epiphany.
The worId is made of two types of women:
The ''simpIe'' girIs and the ''Katie'' girIs.
I'm a ''Katie'' girI and where are our drinks?
I aIways cry at the Iast scene
in that movie...
-...when she sees him with his new wife--
-The simpIe girI.
-And she reaches up--
-And smoothes his hair away.
She says to him:
''Your girI is IoveIy, HubbeII.''
Then the music comes in.
''Memories''
Oh my, God, it's so good.
''Light the corners of my mind
''Misty water-coIored memories
''Of the way we were''
Let me do my favorite part.
-''Can it be''
-Yes!
''Can it be that it was aII so simpIe then
''Or has time re-written every Iine?
''If we had the chance to do it aII again
''TeII me
''WouId we?
''CouId we?
''Memories''
I miss James.
Excuse me?
After I left my frlends, I found myself
pulled to the slte of the engagement party.
I had no lntentlon of golng ln,
but lt was on my way home.
One second.
I had a cholce.
I could run or I could stand
and ask hlm the questlon...
...that lf I dldn't ask,
would haunt me the rest of my llfe.
I thought by the time I got here,
I'd know what to say.
And?
You're Iate.
The party's over.
I'II say it is.
Funny.
I was just on my way home and....
I have a question for you.
Why wasn't it me?
-Carrie--
-No, seriousIy.
I reaIIy need to hear you say it.
Come on, be a friend.
I don't know.
It just got so hard...
...and she's....
Yeah.
''Your girI is IoveIy, HubbeII.''
I don't get it.
And you never did.
Easy, girI.
Then I had a thought,
maybe I dldn't break Blg.
Maybe the problem was
he couldn't break me.
Maybe some women
aren't meant to be tamed.
Maybe they need to run free
untll they flnd someone...
...just as wlld to run wlth.
欲望城市
（性爱专家凯莉布雷萧）
’这时我终于明白’
人生总是不停在做选择
有些选择很重大
好比说跟谁结婚
但有些则更加重大
买五块钱维持三天的
还是十块钱维持五天的？
-都好
-买三天的
五块钱
另一个选择是如何面对前男友
有些女人很冷静，而有些则…
妈的，是史蒂夫
快走…
赔我五块钱，回来
他看起来很受伤
像那些画中的孩子
-可怜的史蒂夫
-对不起，我一时慌了
我不想跟他聊天气之类的话题
我跟那男人上过床
-再给我一包低糖好吗？
-我没办法跟旧情人做朋友
我碰到和前男友维持友谊的人
就会想「她们怎么做到的？」
我从来不跟男人做朋友
要友谊找女人就好
男人是用来上床的
-你得学著有自己的主张
-友谊是额外的好处
如果他们不想谈感情
那就做不成朋友了
-你收回友谊作为惩罚？
-你干嘛讲那么难听
黑寡妇蜘蛛办完事后
便把伴侣的头咬下来
收回友谊可以让他们自在离开
免了分手那幕，你说「过来」
然后大口把他们的头咬下来
我很欣赏那种
「我们相爱过，谢谢你丰富
我的生命，现在各奔前程吧」
但我比较像是
「我们合不来，你最好消失」
-怎么了？
-真的好幼稚
不是说你，是整个情况
我们留著再也不穿的衣服
却把前男友像垃圾一样仍掉
我不是说我自己处理得多好
我还无法跟大人物做朋友
但若你爱过一个人然后分手了
那份爱到哪儿去了？
-移情到下一个女友身上
-不…那是不一样的爱
我跟大人物之间的感情
绝对和他与娜塔莎之间不同
你甚么时候开始不再叫她
「缺少灵魂的空洞白痴」？
大约三周前我在餐厅见到他们
他握著她的手微笑
我终于明白了
他们很快乐，我们结束了
而我觉得没关系
-娜塔莎？甚么烂名字
-一点也没错
-愚蠢
-烂到极点
当晚，我思考著「Ｘ」因子
在数学中，Ｘ代表未知数
Ａ加Ｂ等于Ｘ
但未知的是甚么加甚么
会等于和前男友的友谊？
这是个无解的方程式吗？
或者有没有可能
将昔日热烈的感情
转化成一份恰好的友谊？
我不禁纳闷
和旧情人可以做朋友吗？
星期天下午当米兰达坐在家中
享受著饼乾和报纸…
她前男友就站在外面
我听见你的呼吸声
嗨
你从我面前跑开真是恶劣
-我没有跑
-你有
-我没想到会看见你，而且…
-那真的伤了我的心
我不知道该怎么和前男友相处
米兰达，是我…史蒂夫
你入睡时是我抱著你的头
对不起，我很抱歉
没关系…
我们好久没见面，我很想你
但我却做了这么恶劣的事
-没那么恶劣，真的
-有，我是个恶劣的人
-你不是个恶劣的人
-我很恶劣
你绝不会做出这么恶劣的事
那我跑来你家骂你恶劣
又怎么说？
-没错，那挺恶劣的
-你鼻涕快流出来了
我很想你
每当有好笑的事发生
我总是想告诉你
那就告诉我，我们当不成情人
不表示不能像朋友
偶尔一起吃个饭，对吧？
-是
-你星期五要做甚么？
-我有约会了
-你很期待吧？
正当米兰达计划和前男友
一起吃晚餐
夏绿蒂面对记忆中的初恋…
她的爱马，泰迪
夏绿蒂和泰迪的关系
悲伤地结束
它在一场比赛中将她摔下马
害她摔断锁骨，并且输掉冠军
她父亲把泰迪卖给别人
从那时起她再也没骑过马
夏绿蒂考虑
是否到了该重回马鞍的时候
同时，在城的另一头
莎曼珊即将棋逢对手
我非告诉你不可，你好漂亮
-不好意思，我们认识吗？
-还没有
但改天或许你愿意
跟我共进晚餐？
-你凭甚么认为我会答应？
-从你注视我的眼神
你的率直可以得十分
-我也得到你的电话了吗？
-我还不确定
这样吧
这是我的名片，你跟我联络
公然在大街上和女人搭讪
-你怎么会这么自大？
-我想是天生的吧
至少考虑出来跟我喝一杯
交个朋友
我会的，自大先生
请尽管这么做
当我发现衣柜里还挂著一件
大约1988年的旧洋装时
我决定是时候打电话给前男友
伸出友谊之手
我没料到会是那个缺少灵魂的
空洞白痴接的电话
接著我想起
大人物家有来电显示
该死
-你好
-刚才是你打的吗？
不…对，但我还没来得及讲话
因为…我不小心撞到…东西
所以挂断了，没错，是我打的
我听到娜塔莎的声音
替我向她道个歉
娜塔莎好吗？
她很好
-你好吗
-我一切顺利
-你的语气听起来傻呼呼的
-拜托，你不能放过我一次吗
-这很怪，分手后第一次联络
-没错
也许我照著准备的讲稿念
会好一点
你有讲稿？
我在想…
不知道你觉得…
别再假装彼此不存在
我们试著做朋友如何？
我很乐意
我本来要打给你
但我不知道你想不想接我电话
-你愿意一起吃午餐吗？
-我们一起吃午餐吧
我订了一点的位子，布雷萧
以前我习惯报大人物的名字
但今天我用自己的名字订位
这是朋友的做法
另一位已经到了
你饿了吗？我很饿
我六点就起床，几乎没吃早餐
这里的玉米沙拉很棒
-你说呢？可以吃饭了吗？
-我们吃饭吧
我那时发现到：大人物很紧张
奇怪的是，身为新朋友
这部分的我觉得非常同情
但过去当女朋友那部分的我
却觉得沾沾自喜
-你还好吧？
-没事
-你看起来气色很好
-谢谢，你也是
午安
-这儿的玉米沙拉很好吃
-请问需要甚么饮料？
-冰茶
-矿泉水
-威士忌
-柯梦波丹
一小时后
我已解开了无解的友谊方程式
答案似乎是…
柯梦波丹加上威士忌
等于和前男友的友谊
-老天
-还有你的音乐
我终于不必再听
「血汗泪合唱团」了
-他们的音乐很棒
-起床后十分钟听那种东西？
好了…跟我说说你女朋友的事
-真的？
-朋友之间会谈论感情生活
说吧，朋友
谈谈你女朋友的事
她很温柔…
够了，别跟我说她的事
我听不下去
我们订个协议吧
除非是很认真的感情
否则我们不跟对方说
凯莉…
这次是认真的
我们订婚了
我希望由我亲口告诉你
-我现在头痛欲裂
-我不知道该怎么告诉你
-当你打来时…
-订婚？
你怎么可能订婚？
你这个人恐惧承诺，记得吗？
事实上
你跟我说你再也不想结婚了
-事情会改变
-你只是不想娶我？
-听著，娜塔莎和我…
-别在我面前提她的名字
你玩弄了我两年
然后才过五个月
你就要娶一个25岁的女人
-我没有玩弄你
-随便，好，你没有
我要走了，我头很痛
-你没事吧？
-我很好
别碰我，不要你帮忙
-凯莉，等一下，别走
-你还想干嘛？
-别这样离去
-是你造成的
我想保持友谊
但这种结束方式似乎好得多
去吧，尽管订婚，跟那个叫…
娜金斯基还是甚么的女人结婚
不用管我，我好得很
这些阶梯很危险
隔天，我答应夏绿蒂
在她尝试骑马时要陪著她
-我也需要她的支持
-你还好吗？
除了我前男友
跟一个年轻小妞订婚
而我价值三百块的鞋子
沾到马粪？
我很好
我觉得你很坚强
换做是我可能已进了医院
-它到底有甚么毛病？
-它只是性情倔强
有些马不喜欢被骑
泰迪一开始也是这样
但它一旦被我驯服就很温驯
你知道吗？我驯服了大人物
现在那缺少灵魂的空洞白痴
却坐享其成
凯莉，我真的很难过
我知道，亲爱的，谢了
该死，现实就是如此
你试著跟前男友做朋友
最后却弄得自己一身屎
太好了
这是派尔，它很乖
它是棕色的，泰迪也是
但它腹部有白色的斑点
等我上马之后你就可以走了
好吗？
我会等你，在这里很愉快
去玩吧
-派尔
-脚踩著马蹬然后上去
当夏绿蒂把脚套进马蹬时
所有关于泰迪
摔断骨头以及痛失冠军的
可怕记忆全涌上心头
不行
我做不到
不，我没办法，我们走吧
-我说我没办法
-它已经套上马鞍了
几通电话之后
莎曼珊答应自大先生的邀约
出去喝一杯
到最后已经超越朋友的界线
我从来不在街上钓凯子
除非他们非常迷人
过来吧，你这迷人的家伙
在我们更进一步之前
我得警告你一件事
甚么事？
-我本钱很雄厚
-中头奖了
我是说真的
它很大
大多数的女人无法接受
我不是大多数的女人
拉下拉…过来吧
莎曼珊突然明白
为甚么自大先生会如此骄傲了
那彷佛整面肉墙向我直扑而来
没甚么比一根大棒子
冲向你更可怕
我的嘴巴根本不想靠近它
我怕会肌肉痉挛
我真的很吃惊，他的手算小的
-别告诉我你信那一套？
-现在不信了
再试一次前我得为自己打打气
-你还要再试一次？为甚么？
-因为它就在那里
-只是命根子不是埃佛勒斯峰
-如果它是埃佛勒斯峰
昨晚我才刚登上基地营呢
之前你和大人物交往
现在我和「超大人物」约会
真是难以置信
你因詹姆斯尺寸太小和他分手
现在这个又太大
你是谁？性爱女神吗？
我理想中的对象要刚刚好
当晚，一顿友好的晚餐后
史蒂夫和米兰达
开始探索他们的新友谊
如果你真的是朋友
你会让我留著它
你得把我消防队的Ｔ恤还给我
-我穿非常合身
-去跟法官说吧
-拜托？
-不行
-谢谢你答应出来吃晚餐
-谢谢均KA终于肯让我付钱
朋友是这样的，不是吗？
晚安
对，朋友是这样的，不是吗？
我还有一个问题要问你
朋友会亲…
这里吗？
不会
朋友会亲这里吗？
那朋友会亲…
会
我们分手有很好的理由对吧？
没错，金钱、未来计划、目标
好理由
那现在呢？
-我们仍只是朋友吗？
-对，我们仍只是朋友
会上床的朋友
在这城市的另一头…
-准备好了吗？
-等等
等等
上完两堂进阶瑜珈课
以及抽了她所能找到最棒的烟
莎曼珊准备好
再次挑战埃佛勒斯峰
来吧
慢慢来
就是这样
慢慢来…
轻一点
很好
太棒了
要开始了
要开始了？
你是说你还没进去？
-还没
-停下来
老天
我们能不能只当朋友就好？
就这样，莎曼珊交了生平
第一个男性朋友
隔天在中央公园
夏绿蒂也在交朋友
她觉得她和派尔进展太快了
他们应该把步调放慢
多认识彼此
你很乖，派尔，那样舒服吗？
你喜欢吗？我的泰迪也很喜欢
我好爱我的泰迪，好马儿
她的新夥伴轻轻推了她一下
使夏绿蒂对泰迪的反感消失了
她回想起过去
她曾经多爱它漂亮的白色斑点
放轻松…
走吧
-我是凯莉，我出门买鞋了
-是我，你在家吗？
如果你在家就接电话
你不在家
我打来是想说
上星期的事我觉得很抱歉
我不是有意造成那种局面
你必须知道这件事
而我不想让别人告诉你
老天，我觉得自己很混帐
对不起，我真的很抱歉
你知道我绝不会故意伤害你
我知道你不会
-原来你在家？
-对，我在家
-那…就像我说的，我很抱歉
-我也很抱歉
我不该有那么大反应
我只是…
这消息让我很震惊
我想这是必要的打击
好让我继续往前走
是
我衷心祝福你，真的
我希望你和娜塔莎过得很幸福
-那是真心话吗？
-不是
但我会的，真的，我希望…
将来有一天，很快…
我们大家能一起出来喝东西
当好朋友
就像电影里演的那样
那么…
再见了
再见
事实上，我真的打算
维持那份友好的感觉，直到…
（我们订婚了）
我不敢相信我的前男友
现在正在六条街外的饭店
举行订婚宴
我不敢相信他竟然有脸邀请你
那是我的错，是我自己
要对他发表「友好宣言」
我在开甚么玩笑？我们从来
都不是朋友，我们是其他关系
显然是那种最后不会在饭店
举行订婚派对的关系
还要再一轮饮料吗？
麻烦再来四杯
我想我可以感觉到
他们正在那边吃虾子
只是…为甚么是她？
说真的，为甚么是她？
-一句话：赫伯
-赫伯
我的天，赫伯
没错，真的好赫伯
-谁是赫伯？
-赫伯
劳勃瑞福在「往日情怀」中
饰演的赫伯
-我好爱那部电影
-我超…超爱那部电影
-没看过
-我的天
你怎么可能没看过
「往日情怀」？
少女看的片子
劳勃瑞福疯狂地爱著
芭芭拉史翠珊
-凯蒂
-凯…凯蒂
凯…凯蒂，没错
但他不能跟她在一起
因为她太复杂了
而且还有一头狂野的卷发
卷…卷发
所以他离开她
娶了一个直发的单纯女孩
我突然有所领悟
这世界只有两种类型的女人
单纯型和凯蒂型
我就是凯蒂型
饮料到底送来了没？
我每次看那部电影的
最后一幕都会哭
当她在旅馆前
看见他和他新婚妻子
那单纯女孩
-她抬起手…
-拨开他的头发
对他说
「你太太很漂亮，赫伯」
然后音乐进来了
-（回忆…）
-我的天，真好听
（像是我遥远心境的一角）
（往日情怀的…）
（模糊记忆）
我最爱的部分让我来
（是否…）
（是否当时一切都太单纯？）
（或者时光改写了每行诗？）
（如果我们有机会重来）
（告诉我，会有结果吗？）
（可能吗？）
我想念詹姆斯
你说甚么？
和朋友们散会后，我发现自己
不由自主往订婚派对的
地点走去
我并不想进去
但那在我回家的路上
等我一会
我有个选择
我可以跑走，或问他一个…
如果不问
会困扰我一辈子的问题
我以为在我到达之前
我就会知道该说甚么
然后呢？
你迟到了，派对结束了
我想是吧
有意思
我只是回家时顺路经过
我有个问题要问你
为甚么不是我？
不，我是认真的
我真的需要听你亲口说
拜托，我们是朋友
我不知道
就是很难
-而她…
-是
你太太很漂亮，赫伯
-我不明白
-你永远也不会明白
别激动
那时我想到
也许我并未驯服大人物
也许问题在于他无法驯服我
也许有些女人注定不该被驾驭
也许她们需要自由奔驰
直到她们找到…
性情相投的伴侣一起同行